{
    "subject": "resource/Pleurotomella_marshalli",
    "predicate": "ontology/family",
    "object": "resource/Raphitomidae",
    "human_readable": "Pleurotomella marshalli is a member of the family Raphitomidae.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9886487126350403,
            "question": "Is Pleurotomella marshalli a member of the Raphitomidae family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.974262535572052,
            "question": "Name a family that Pleurotomella marshalli belongs to."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9524006843566895,
            "question": "To which family does Pleurotomella marshalli belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9331366419792175,
            "question": "What is the family name of Pleurotomella marshalli?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9286115765571594,
            "question": "Pleurotomella marshalli is classified under which family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9131703972816467,
            "question": "What family name is associated with Pleurotomella marshalli?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9109312891960144,
            "question": "Which family does the organism Pleurotomella marshalli belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9032273888587952,
            "question": "Give an example of a family that includes Pleurotomella marshalli."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8880864381790161,
            "question": "What is the taxonomic family of Pleurotomella marshalli?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7749716639518738,
            "question": "What is the taxonomic classification of Pleurotomella marshalli at the family level?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pleurotomella marshalli is a member of the family Raphitomidae.",
            "html": "dbpedia_207_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the taxonomic family of Pleurotomella marshalli?",
            "html": "dbpedia_207_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Give an example of a family that includes Pleurotomella marshalli.",
            "html": "dbpedia_207_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which family does the organism Pleurotomella marshalli belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_207_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_207_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_207_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_207_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_207_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_207_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_207_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_207_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_207_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_207_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_207_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's my evaluation:\n\nThe triple to be evaluated is:\nPleurotomella marshalli is a member of the family Raphitomidae.\n\nAccording to the context information, especially from the file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_207/re-ranker-msmarco/1.txt, the document mentions:\n\"English: Pleurotomella marshalli (Sykes, 1906); family Raphitomidae; Portugal.\"\n\nThis information supports the triple. Therefore:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe context information provided mentions \"Pleurotomella marshalli (Sykes, 1906); family Raphitomidae,\" which supports the statement that Pleurotomella marshalli is a member of the family Raphitomidae."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}